reesesfanup.com 2016-04-05

# The Hershey Company | Privacy Policy

##             Effective Date: December 05, 2014 (last updated 12/05/2014)

## **Privacy Policy applies to several of our sites and apps.**

This policy describes our privacy practices for the websites and mobile applications where it is posted. This includes the _Hershey’s Chocolate World_ website and Hershey brand websites, as well as [_Hershey’s_ Kitchens](http://www.hersheykitchens.com/) and Celebrate with _Hershey’s_. This includes mobile websites. The policy also describes our practices on our smart phone applications. This policy does not apply to information we collect offline. This policy also does not apply to the websites of [Hershey Entertainment and Resorts Company](http://www.hersheypa.com/) , including [The Hotel Hershey](http://www.thehotelhershey.com/) and [Hersheypark ](http://www.hersheypark.com/). It also does not apply to the Hershey Park mobile app.

To download a copy of this full privacy policy, [click here.]

## **We collect information from and about you.**

**Contact information:** For example, we might collect your name and zip code. We might also collect your state or email. 

**Payment information:** If you make purchases, we or our vendors might collect your credit card information.

**Information you submit or post:** If you post content, apply for a job, or respond to a survey, we will collect the information you provide to us.

**Demographic information:** We may collect gender. We might also ask for information like your age.

**Other Information:** If you use our websites, we may collect information about the browser you are using. We might track the pages you visit. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. We collect this information using the tracking tools described here. To control those tools, please read here. The information may include GPS locations for our mobile apps.

## **We collect information in different ways.**

**We collect information directly from you.** For example, if you register for a promotion or apply for a job. We might also collect information if you post a recipe review or contact us. We may also collect information if register for certain sites.

**We collect information from you passively.** We may use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. To learn more about these tools and how you can control them, click here.

**We get information about you from third parties.** For example, social media platforms may give us information about you. 

## **We use information as disclosed and described here.**

**We use information to respond to your requests or questions.** For example, we might use your information to register you for promotions. We also use your information to respond to you when you contact us. 

**We use information for marketing purposes.** For example, we might send you information about new products and special offers. We might also use your information to serve you ads about products and offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. We will send you marketing emails if you sign-up. To manage this, read [Your Choices](https://www.hersheys.com/account/login.aspx) section below. We may also use push notifications on our mobile apps.

**We use information to improve our products and services.** We might use your information to customize your experience with us. 

**We use information to look at site trends and customer interests.** We may use your information to make website or product improvements. We may also combine information we get from you with information about you we have gotten from third parties.

**We use information for security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our websites.

**We use information to promote us and our various websites.** Unless we tell you otherwise, we might send you notices of special promotions, offers or solicitations. We might tell you about new website features or product offerings. To manage this, follow the instructions in [Your Choices](https://www.hersheys.com/account/login.aspx), below. 

**We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship:** We may contact you to tell you about changes to this Policy or our website Terms. We may also tell you about issues with your orders. 

**We use information to talk to parents or guardians to get permission.** We may use contact information to get permission from parents for children who want to use our site.

**We use information as otherwise permitted by law.**

## **We may share information with third parties.**

**We will share information within our company (including our affiliated companies).**

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law.** For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. 

**We will share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business was sold we may sell our customer list as part of that transaction.

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.** For example, we share information with vendors, or will authorize them to collect information on our behalf. Some vendors may be located outside of the United States.

**We will share information with our business partners.** For example, we might share information with a business partner who is running a joint promotion with us. We might also share information with a business partner who distributes our products. To opt out of having your information shared, see the [Your Choices](https://www.hersheys.com/account/login.aspx) section below. 

**We will share information with Hershey Entertainment and Resorts Company.** For example, sometimes we receive questions about The Hotel Hershey or Hersheypark. We may share information so they can address those questions.

**We will share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

## **You have certain choices about our marketing and tracking tools.**

**You can opt out of marketing emails.** To stop receiving our promotional emails, follow the opt-out link in any of our promotional emails or call us at 1 (800) 468-1714. 

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.** We may use tracking tools and cookies. To learn how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools on our ecommerce sites, please click here

**You have other controls you can exercise.** You can choose whether or not to share personal information. If you choose not to share, some parts of our sites and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use. If you turn off cookies or tracking tools, parts of our site and services may also not work properly

## **These sites and children.**

Our e-commerce sites are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 on-line without first obtaining permission from the child's parent or guardian. 

We do not require a child to provide more personally identifiable information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity. 

Parents, you can review information about your child that we have on file, or request that certain information be changed or deleted, please contact:

The Hershey Company   
Consumer Relations   
100 Crystal A Drive   
Hershey, PA 17033

Phone Toll Free 1-800-468-1714, or Contact us [Online](http://www.thehersheycompany.com/contact-us.aspx)

For information from the Federal Trade Commission about protecting children's privacy on-line, [click here.](http://www.ftc.gov/news-events/press-releases/2002/04/ftc-protecting-childrens-privacy-online)

## **We use standard security measures.**

The Internet is not 100% secure, though. We thus cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.

## **We store information in the United States.**

If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States and by using the Sites/giving your information, you consent to such transfer, and understand that the U.S. may not provide the same level of protections as the laws of your country. 

## **We may link to third party sites or services we don’t control.**

If you click on one of those links, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the information practices of that website. You should read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for such third party's sites.

## **Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.**

You can Contact us Online or write to us at: 

Public Relations Department   
The Hershey Company   
PO Box 810   
100 Crystal A Drive   
Hershey, PA 17033 

You can also call us at 1-800-468-1714 

You can review the information we have collected about you or your child by [Contacting Us Online.](http://www.thehersheycompany.com/contact-us.aspx)

Copyright © The Hershey Company
